{"data":[{"question":"The mausoleum is ________ by Thien Thu mountain, two towering columns and a vast expanse of water.","a":"feed","b":"feeding","c":"fed","d":"feeds","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Passive voice: be + past participle","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Put plants ________ a window so that they will get enough light.","a":"near to","b":"near of","c":"next to","d":"nearly","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Next to (proposition): very close to someone or something, with nothing in between.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Employers often require that candidates have not only a degree ________.","a":"but two years experience","b":"also two years experience","c":"but also two-year experience","d":"but more two years experience","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Structure: Not only...but also...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Richard Nixon had been a lawyer and ________ before he entered politics.","a":"served in the Navy as an officer","b":"an officer in the Navy","c":"the Navy had him as an officer","d":"did service in the Navy as an officer","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Parallel structure: structure before and after \"and\" must be nouns of careers","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"If one of the participants in a conversation wonders ________ no real communication has taken place.","a":"what said the other person","b":"what the other person said","c":"what did the other person say","d":"what was the other person saying","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Narrative sentence: S + V + O (what the other person said)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The salary of a bus driver is much higher ________.","a":"in comparison with the salary of a teacher","b":"than a teacher","c":"than that of a teacher","d":"to compare as a teacher","answer":"3","explain":"\n- We use the comparative form of short adjective (high)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Professional people expect ________ when it is necessary to cancel an appointment.","a":"you to call them","b":"that you would call them","c":"your calling them","d":"that you are calling them","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Expect somebody to do something = want somebody to do something\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Sedimentary rocks are formed below the surface of the earth ________ very high temperatures and pressures.","a":"where there are","b":"there are","c":"where are there","d":"there are where","answer":"1","explain":"\n- What\/where\/ which... can be use as a relative pronoun. Relative pronouns introduce relative clauses, which are a type of dependent clause.\u00a0\n- Dependent clause followed by relative pronoun (who\/whom\/which\/where...) is narrative sentence: S + V + O.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Farmers look forward to ________ every summer.","a":"participating in the county fairs","b":"participate in the county fairs","c":"be participating in the county fairs","d":"have participated in the county fairs","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Look forward to + Verb_ing.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Clipper ships were the swiftest sailing ships that ________ to sea and the most beautiful.","a":"ever were put","b":"were ever putted","c":"were ever put","d":"ever were putted","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Structure: To be + adv (ever, never, often, sometimes...). + PII\n- Irregular Verb: Put- Put- Put.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}